A Guide to the Papers of James Washington Singleton 1770-1975
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Series I: Correspondence (Box Boxes 1-21)
  - Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn (1857-1943)
    - Correspondence June-August, 1928 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence September-October, 1928 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence November-December, 1928 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence January-May, 1929 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence June-September, 1929 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence October-December, 1929 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence March-June, 1930 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence July-September, 1930 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence October-November, 1930 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence December, 1930 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence January-February, 1931 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence March-April, 1931 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence May-December, 1931 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence January-April, 1932 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence May-December, 1932 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence February-May, 1933 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence June-October, 1933 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence January-June, 1934 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence September-December, 1934 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence January-August, 1935 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence September-November, 1935 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence December, 1935 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence January, 1936 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence February, 1936 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence March-June, 1936 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence September-December, 1936 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence 1937 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence 1938 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1939 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence 1940 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence 1942 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 13)
  - James Jones Singleton (1860-1948)
    The correspondence of James Jones Singleton (1860-1948) dating from 1891 to 1906. The correspondence for the most part pertains to the death of his father in 1892 and the death of his mother in 1902.
    - Correspondence 1891 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence 1892 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence 1894-1906 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Louise Singleton Thomas Kemp (1884-1969)
    The correspondence of Louise Singleton Thomas Kemp (1884-1969) dating from 1890 to 1911. The subseries is composed of the childhood correspondence of Lily's eldest daughter, Louise.
    - Correspondence 1890-1896, 1905-1909 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1910-1911 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Judith Ball Thomas Wysong (1887-1976)
    The correspondence of Judith Ball Thomas Wysong (1887-1976) dating from 1894 to1923 is the childhood correspondence of Lily's daughter Judith.
    - Correspondence 1894, 1896 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence October, 1910 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence November-December, 1910 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1911-1912 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 1915-November 24, 1919 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence November 25, 1919-1920, 1923 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Francis Worthington Thomas, Jr. (1889-1910)
    Correspondence of Francis Worthington Thomas, Jr. (1889-1910) dating from 1908 to 1910 is the letters of Lily's only son Francis.
    - Correspondence 1908-1909 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1910 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Cora Eller Thomas (1894-1962)
    The correspondence of Cora Elder Thomas dating 1906-1918 consists of a few letters of Lily's youngest daughter Cora.
    - Correspondence 1906, 1910, 1912, 1918 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Judith Ball Wysong Cofer (1924- )
    The correspondence of Judith Ball Wysong Cofer (1924- ) dating from 1959 to 1975 includes one folder of letters from researchers requesting access to the Singleton papers or information on James W. Singleton.
    - Correspondence 1959-1975 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Parthenia Marie Thomas deLoach (1892- )
    The correspondence of Parthenia Marie Thomas de Loach (1892- ) dating from 1908 to 1936.
    - Correspondence 1908-1909 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1910 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1911-1913, 1917-1919 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Letters from PMTD 1898-1921 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Letters from PMTD 1922 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Letters from PMTD January-March, 1923 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Letters from PMTD April-July, 1923 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Letters from PMTD August-December, 1923 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Letters from PMTD January-April, 1924 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Letters from PMTD May-December, 1924 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Letters from PMTD January-April, 1925 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Letters from PMTD May-December, 1925 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Letters from PMTD January-July, 1926 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Letters from PMTD August-December, 1926 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Letters from PMTD February-July, 1927 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Letters from PMTD September-December, 1927 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Letters from PMTD January-July, 1928 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Letters from PMTD September-December, 1928 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Letters from PMTD 1929 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Letters from PMTD 1930 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Letters from PMTD 1931 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Letters from PMTD 1932-1933 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Letters from PMTD 1934 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Letters from PMTD 1935 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Letters from PMTD 1936 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 13)
- Legal and Government Documents
  This series includes agreements, appointments, deeds, indentures, inventories, estate appraisals, licenses, summons, wills, and miscellaneous government documents.
  - Agreements (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Appointments 1893, 1901 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Bills--U.S. House and Senate (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Court Orders (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Deeds (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Estate of Gen. James Singleton, related documents (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Indentures (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Inventories and Estate Appraisals (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Legal Briefs, 1834, 1876, 1908 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Letters Patent (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Presidential Message, 1838 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Report of the Committee of Twenty-Four 1833 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Summons (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Wills (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 15)
- Financial and Bookkeeping Records
  - Daybook ca. 1812 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Daybook ca. 1832 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Daybook 1847 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Receipts and invoices, 1770-1810 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Receipts and invoices, 1811-1815 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Receipts and invoices, 1816-1838 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Receipts and invoices, 1840-1855 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Receipts and invoices, 1860-1869 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Receipts and invoices, 1870-1889 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Receipts and invoices, 1890-1909 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Receipts and invoices, 1910-1925, 1931, 1934, 1941 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Receipts and invoices, Revenue Tax, 1804 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 27)
- Business Papers
  - Farmer's Bank of Virginia at Winchester (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Great Western Railroad Company (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Hannibal and St. Joseph Railroad Company (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Quincy, Alton and St. Louis Railroad Company (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Quincy and Palmyra Railroad Company (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Horse Breeding (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 6)
- Military Papers
  - Abstract, Provisions Paid, 1813 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Commission, 1846 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Inventory, clothing distributed to men under command of James Singleton (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Memorandum of General Washington (a copy) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Orders 1807 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Orders 1814 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Orders 1844 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Organization of the Virginia Militia, 1804 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Payroll, April 12, 1795 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Proclamation (pardoning participants in Whiskey Rebellion) 1794 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Reports, 1795-1814 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 17)
- Speeches
  - Speeches, 1812 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Speeches, 1838 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Speeches, 1871-1872 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Speeches, 1874-1881 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 21)
- Miscellany
  - Materials of Matthew Page Andrews
    - Article--"Abraham Lincoln's Envoy of Peach" (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Article--"Abraham Lincoln's Envoy of Peach" (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Article--"Lincoln's Lost Friend" (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Biographical Information: Abraham Lincoln (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Biographical Information: James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Book Reviews in the Confederate Veteran (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Information on James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 28)
      (Supplied by Mrs. Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn)
    - Interview with Anna Singleton McDonald, December 6, 1928 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous Papers (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Notes, Singleton Paper (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Questions for Mrs. Osburn (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Source Materials (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Source Materials, James Singleton (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Genealogical and Historical Notes Collected by Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn
    - Ball Family (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Fauntleroy Family (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 36)
    - McCarthy Family (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 37)
    - McDonald Family (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 38-39)
    - Singleton Family I-III (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 40-42)
    - Thomas Family (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Throckmorton Family (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Other Families I-IV (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 3-6)
    - Printed genealogical materials (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 7)
    - James Singleton (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 8)
    - James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Other Subjects Arranged Alphabethically
    - Advertisements (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Autobiographical Sketch: James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Biographical Material: James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Biographical Material: James W. Singleton: Chicago Times December 26, 1885 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Church Papers, James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Creative Writings (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Creative Writings: Anna Singleton McDonald (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Diary: James W. Singleton 1870 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Letter to the Editor, Richmond Enquirer ca. 1840 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Insurance Policies 1899-1944 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Inventories (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Poetry (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Poetry: Printed (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Poetry: St. John's Wood (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Poetry: Anna Singleton McDonald (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Poetry: James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Political Papers: James Singleton (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Political Papers I-II: James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 8-9)
    - Reception (lists of food and guests) February 26, 1880 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Report Cards: Lily Singleton (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Report Cards: Louise Singleton Thomas (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Report Cards: Francis W. Thomas, Jr. 1900 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Report Cards: Francis W. Thomas, Jr., Clay Hill Academy 1905-1906 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Report Cards: Francis W. Thomas, Jr., Hampden-Sydney College 1906-1910 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Report Cards: Parthenia M. Thomas, Stephenson Seminary 1907-1910 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Report Cards: Cora E. Thomas, Stephenson Seminary (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Report Cards: Elinor and Willard Osburn (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Restoration of Battle Flags (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Schoolwork: Italian Exercise Book, Lily Singleton (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Schoolwork: The Thomas Children (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Slave Recipe for Beer (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Societies: National Society, United States Daughters of 1812, Pocahontas Memorial Association, Society of the Cincinnati, Washington Club (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Travel Itinerary (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Tributes and Memorials (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Fragments (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Baptismal Certificate: Singleton Van Scharch (copy) (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Address Book: Lily E. Singleton Thomas (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Calling Book: Lily Singleton Thomas (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Booklets, Souvenir (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Booklets, Souvenir, Jefferson County, West Virginia 1801-1851 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Calling Cards (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Calling Cards: James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Greeting Cards (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Clarke County Historical Collection (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Confederate Bonds (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Diploma (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Flowers and Plants (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Locks of Hair (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Invitations, Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Momentoes, Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Momentoes from Boscobel, Boscobel Stock Farm and Singleton Park (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Money and Bank Notes (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Music: Columbia's Call (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Passes (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Pedigree of Airedale Terrier (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Postcards (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Posters Advertising Sale of Land (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Pot Luck Club (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Programs (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Programs: George Washington Bicentennial Ball (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Programs: James Exposition 1907 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Programs: National Music Week 1929 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Programs: Opera (I-X) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 3-12)
    - Programs: Plays (I-II) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 13-14)
    - Recipes (I-V) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 1-5)
    - Scrapbook: 19th Century clippings (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Scrapbook: Clippings 1830-1850 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook: Civil War Momentoes (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Seals (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Valentines (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Wedding Book: Lily Singleton Thomas Howard Osburn (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Wedding Invitations: Louise, Judith and Parthenia Thomas (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Wedding Invitations 1881, 1883, 1903 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Wedding Invitations 1917 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Wedding Invitations 1919, 1921 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Wedding Invitations 1922 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Wedding Invitations 1924-1926 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Wedding Invitations, undated (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Wedding Invitation List: Lily E. Singleton (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Wedding InvitationLists: Louise, Judith and Parthenia Thomas (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 10)
- Newspaper Clippings
  - Ball Family (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Breeden Family (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Civil War Clippings (contemporary) (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Corbyn Family (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Jefferson Davis (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Parthenia Marie Thomas deLoach (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Genealogy I-II (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 17-18)
  - Ulysses S. Grant (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Wade Hampton (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Thomas J. (Stonewall) Jackson (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Louise Singleton Thomas Kemp (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Kircheval Family (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Robert E. Lee (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Abraham Lincoln I-III (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 25-27)
  - McDannold Family (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 1)
  - McDonald Family (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Marshall Family (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 3)
  - George C. Marshall (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous(I-X) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 5-14)
  - Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Quincy, Illinois and Winchester, Virgina (I-II) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 16-17)
  - Sherrard Family (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Singleton Family (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 1)
  - James Jones Singleton (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 2)
  - James W. Singleton (I-V) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 3-7)
  - James W. Singleton: Silver Heels (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 8)
  - James W. Singleton: Tributes (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 9)
  - James W. Singleton: 20th Century Articles (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Parthenia Singleton (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Francis Worthington Thomas (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Washington Family (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Daniel Webster (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Woodrow Wilson (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Judith Ball Thomas Wysong (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous clippings 1851 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous clippings 1855 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous clippings 1856 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous clippings 1859 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous clippings 1860 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous clippings 1861 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 22-23)
  - Miscellaneous clippings 1862 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous clippings 1864 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous clippings 1865 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 26)
- Publications
  - General
    - Almanac 1802 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Art Club of Philadelphia 1891 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Burnett's Floral Handbook (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Cord Stunts for Kiddies 1921 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Columbia: The Land of the Free (Anna Singleton McDonald) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 5)
    - The Complaint, or Night Thoughts (Edward Young) 1840 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 6)
    - The Constant Christmas (Phillips Brooks) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Early History of the Daughters of the American Revolution (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Eulenspiegl Und Munchhausen (Peter Hagboldt) 1933 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Ford's History of Illinois (Governor Thomas Ford) 1854 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 10)
    - French Language Guide 1943 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Greek and Roman Mythology (Lloyd E. Smith) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 12)
    - History of Indian Pottery (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Hand Book of Washington Cathedral 1911 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Holy Thoughts and Prayers (Dr. Hook) 1849 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Luther Martin: The "Federal Bull Dog" and a Sketch of the Life and Character of Nathaniel Ramsay 1887 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Maryland Life Insurance Almanac 1899 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 5)
    - My Mother-in-Law, Bricktop ca. 1875 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 6)
    - A Neglected Phase of Revolutionary History 1945 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 7)
    - New York As It Is, In 1833 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Popular Synonyms (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 9)
    - The Privateeisman: Captain Manvot (Charles J. Finger) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 1)
    - The Relations of the United States to Each Other as Modified by the War and the Constitutional Amendments (John Randolph Tucker) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Some Emigrants to Virginia (W. G. Standard) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 3)
    - To Cuba and Back: A Variation Voyage (Richard H. Dana) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Wanderer in Washington 1827 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 5)
    - A Young Veteran of the War (Anna Morgan Getyendanner) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Serials
    - Harper's New Monthly Magazine, No. 69 February 1856 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Harper's New Monthly Magazine, No. 392 January 1883 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Harper's New Monthly Magazine, No. 394 March 1883 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Harper's New Monthly Magazine, No. 395 April 1883 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 10)
    - The Prophetic Times, Vol. VI, Nos. 8-9 1868 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Quarterly Journal 1863 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Quincy Motor Club Exhaust, Vol. II, Nos. 1-2 1924 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 13)
- Photographs
  - Ambrotypes and Daguerreotypes
    - Edward C. McDonald (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Joseph H. Sherrard and Ann with daughter Lizzie (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Sherrard (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Prints
    - Reid Baker (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Ball Coat of Arms (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Boscobel (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Jamie Stinson Breedin (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Louise Breedin (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Celeste Buford (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Chapel Green (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Joseph Sherrard Coleman (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Lucy Singleton Coleman (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 13)
    - William Corbyn (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Francis Bratten deLoach (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Home of General Daniel Morgan (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Homes of General James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Louise Singleton Thomas Kemp (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Millicent McDonald (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Florence McElroy (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Frances Buford McElroy (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Mary Frances Buford McElroy (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Buford Mott (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Old Chapel (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 24)